let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which of the following rocks in not an <b>Extrusive Igneous Rock</b>?",
    answer: "Gabbro",
    options: [
      "Basalt",
      "Pumice",
      "Gabbro",
      "Andestine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the thickness of the Earth's Mantle <b>(This is an Approximate?",
    answer: "2900 km",
    options: [
      "3486 km",
      "1216 km",
      "2900 km",
      "1000 km"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is caused due to endogenic forces ?",
    answer: "Upliftment",
    options: [
      "Deposition",
      "Erosion",
      "Upliftment",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the full-form of <b>SDG </b>?",
    answer: "Sustainable Development Goals",
    options: [
      "Sustainable Development Goals",
      "Sustainable Degedation Goals",
      "Sustainable Deforestation Goals",
      "Sustainable Development Games"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The point Inside the earth where the Eartquake occurs is known as ________________?",
    answer: "Focus",
    options: [
      "Epicentre",
      "tectonic Plates",
      "Sesmic Wave",
      "Focus"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which layer comes after <b>Thermosphere</b>?",
    answer: "Exosphere",
    options: [
      "Troposphere",
      "Exosphere",
      "Stratosphere",
      "Mesosphere"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which step comes after <b>Condensation</b> in the <b> Water Cycle</b>?",
    answer: "Precipitation",
    options: [
      "Evaporation",
      "Transpiration",
      "Precipitation",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "_____________ are the diturbances on the surface of sea, in the form of a moving Ridge or Swell.(Complete the following sentence",
    answer: "Waves",
    options: [
      "Waves",
      "Tsunami",
      "Ocean Currents",
      "Flood"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What refers to the water present on Earth?",
    answer: "Hydrosphere",
    options: [
      "Atmosphere",
      "Biosphere",
      "Lithosphere",
      "Hydrosphere",
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Whcih of the following rocks is an example of a <b> Sedimentry Rock</b>?",
    answer: "Limestone",
    options: [
      "Limestone",
      "Slate",
      "Marble",
      "Diorite"
    ]
  },



];